Office of the Dean of Undergraduate Students Records, 1907-2015: Finding Aid AC136
University Archives
- Series 2: Student Activities and Organizations, 1940-1997; 16 boxes; 1 folder
  - 1970-1982, 1970-1986; 2 boxes
    - Camerata, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Chamber Orchestra, 1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Chess Club, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Chicano Press Club, 1980-1986; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Chicano Caucus, 1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Christian Science Organization, 1975; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - College Bowl, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - College Conservatives, 1981; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Community Development and Self-Reliance Group, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Committee on El Salvador, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Committee on the Soviet Threat, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Committee for the Support of Solidarity, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Committee to Oppose United States Intervention in Central America, 1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Concordia Society, 1981; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - C. S. Lewis Society of Princeton University, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Cricket Club, 1980; 1 box (Box 33)
    - Cycling Team and Touring Club, 1979-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Daily Princetonian, 1975-1981; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - Dance Team, 1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - Darts Club, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - Princeton Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee, 1981; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 51)
    - Princeton University Democrats, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 52)
    - Princeton Draft Information Organization, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 53)
    - Drum/The Restroom Wall, 1981; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 54)
    - Engineering Council, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 55)
    - Environmental Action Group, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 56)
    - Erhard Seminars Training, 1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 57)
    - Equestrian Club, 1978-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 58)
    - Expressions, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 59)
    - Men's Field Hockey Team, 1981; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 60)
    - Film Society, 1974-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 61)
    - World Folkdance Cooperative, 1979-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 62)
    - Fishing Club, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 63)
    - Focus on Youth, 1974-1981; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 64)
    - Footnotes, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 65)
    - Forerunner Magazine, 1976-1981; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 66)
    - Foundation for Student Communication, 1975-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 67)
    - Forum for International Communication, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 68)
    - Frontier Missions Society, 1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 69)
    - Gay Alliance of Princeton, 1976-1985; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 70)
    - Glee Club, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 71)
    - Go Club, 1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Gospel Ensemble, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Women's Gymnastics, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Men's Gymnastics, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Harambee House, 1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Holistic Health Association,1982, undated; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Hunger Action, 1977; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Imhotep, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Infinity Limited, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - International Student's Association of Princeton, 1975-1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Islanders Production Group, 1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Inquiry, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - The Journal, 1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Journal of the Princeton University School of Architecture, 1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Jazz Ensemble, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Jewish Theater Project, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Judo Club, 1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Shotokan Karate Club, 1978-1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Karate Club, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Katzenjammers, 1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Keyceptors, 1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Korean Students Association, 1978-1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Kuumba, 1974-1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Latino Women's Group, 1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Latter-Day Saints Student Association of Princeton, 1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Libertarian Organization, 1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Mime Company, 1979-1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Models and Miniatures, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Mobilization for Survival, 1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Mountaineering, 1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Music Co-op, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - The Madison Report, 1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Nassau Literary Review, 1980-1977; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Nassau Weekly, 1979-1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Princeton Journal of the Arts and Sciences, 1976-1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Tiger Magazine, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Madrigal Society, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Nassoons, 1971-1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Nexus, 1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - National Organization for the Reform of Marijuana Laws (NORML), 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - The Offbeats, 1979; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Organization of Black Unity, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - Olden Art Cooperative, 1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 43)
    - Organization of Native American Students, 1974-1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 44)
    - Powerlifting, 1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 45)
    - Pre-Law Society, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 46)
    - Pre-Med Society, 1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 47)
    - Press Club, 1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 48)
    - Princeton-East Harlem Exchange Program, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 49)
    - Platform Tennis Team, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 50)
    - Pro-Life Coalition, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 51)
    - Progressive Exchange, 1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 52)
    - Princeton to Edinburgh, 1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 53)
    - Cheerleaders, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 54)
    - Psychology Club, 1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 55)
    - Rugby Club, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 56)
    - Return to Innocence, 1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 57)
    - Russian Club, 1978-1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 58)
    - Women's Rugby, 1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 59)
    - Scottish Country Dancers, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 60)
    - Screenwriters, 1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 61)
    - Semper Fidelis Society, 1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 62)
    - Ski Team-Club, 1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 63)
    - Women's Soccer, 1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 64)
    - Society for Creative Anachronism, 1979; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 65)
    - Society of Latino Engineers, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 66)
    - Society of Women Engineers, 1973-1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 67)
    - Society of Black Engineers, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 68)
    - South-East Asian Students Association, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 69)
    - Students for the Exploration and Development of Space, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 70)
    - Students for Progress, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 71)
    - Theatre Intime, 1973-1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 72)
    - Tigerlilies, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 73)
    - Tigertones, 1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 74)
    - Tigressions, 1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 75)
    - Tras, 1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 76)
    - Triangle, 1974-1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 77)
    - Turkish Students Association, 1976-1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 78)
    - Ubiquity, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 79)
    - Ultimate Frisbee, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 80)
    - Unlimited Graphics, 1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 81)
    - WPRB, 1970-1982; 2 folders (Box 34, Folder 82-83)
    - Circle K Club, 1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 84)
    - Social Alternatives Commission, 1977-1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 85)
    - Polish Cultural Society, 1978-1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 86)
    - Dod Hall Food Cooperative, 1973-1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 87)
    - Pre-Med Society, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 88)
    - American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronauts, 1979; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 89)
    - Bowling Club, 1979; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 90)
    - French Club, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 91)
    - Le Club Haitian-American de Princeton, 1979; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 92)
    - Minority Pre-Business, 1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 93)
    - Student Affairs Advisory Board, undated; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 94)
    - Student Health Advisory Board, 1979-1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 95)
    - Soaring Society, 1975; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 96)
    - Chinese Christian Fellowship, 1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 97)
    - Undergraduate Student Government, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 98)
    - University Repulsions, 1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 99)
    - Men's Volleyball Team, 1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 100)
    - Women's Water Polo Team, 1979-1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 101)
    - Men's Water Polo, 1979-1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 102)
    - West Indian Students Association, 1979-1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 103)
    - Yacht Club, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 104)
    - Tai Chi Club, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 105)
    - Young Socialist Alliance, 1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 106)
    - Zen Studies Society, 1981; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 107)
  - 1985-1992, 1973-1996; 3 boxes; 1 folder
    - Princeton Student Pugwash, 1985; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - AIESEC, 1985; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Amateur Radio Club, 1985; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), 1985; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Amigos de Los Ameilas, 1985; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Arnold Air Society, 1985; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Cooperative Co-op, 1985; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Endowment for Divestiture, 1985; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - International Development Organization, 1985; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - International Forum, 1985; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Jugglers, 1985; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Off-Campus Magazine, 1987; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Orchestra, 1986; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Operations Research Society of America, 1989; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Orthodox Christian Fellowship, 1986; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Power, 1986; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Pre-Medical Society, 1986; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Psychology Club, 1986; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Ground-Floor Video, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Television Yearbook, 1986; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Students on Life After Princeton, 1988-1989; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Swedish Student Society, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - SUNY B Psycho Squad, undated; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Theatre Arts Council, 1984; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - World Folk-Dance Cooperative, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous, 1986-1992; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Air Force R.O.T.C., 1986-1994; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - African-American Jewish Alliance, 1992; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - AIDS Quilt, 1994; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Academic Review, Princeton, 1991; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Africa Society, undated; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Alpha-Omega Christian Fellowship, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - American Field Service, 1993-1994; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Apartheid, Students Against, 1989-1990; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - A Room of Our Own, 1991; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Armenian Club of Princeton, undated; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Art Fantasy Association, Princeton, 1989; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - A Room of Our Own, 1991-1993; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Book Exchange, 1992; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Princeton Organization for Ethiopian Jewry, 1990; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Program on Europe, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Black Men for Achievement, 1992; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Bisexual Interest Group, 1992; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Black Freshman Table, 1992; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Buchanan, Students for, 1993; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Campus Naturalists, Princeton, 1992-1993; 2 folders (Box 36, Folder 20-21)
    - Court Appointed Special Advocates (CASA), Students for, 1993; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Chapel Choir, University, 1985-1992; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Club La Amistad, 1992-1993; 2 folders (Box 36, Folder 24-25)
    - Club Care, 1988; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Coalition of Purpose, 1991-1993; 2 folders (Box 36, Folder 26-27)
    - Coeducated Eating Clubs, Organization for, 1989-1991; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Committee to Convince Undergraduate Student Government to Act Responsibly, 1989-1990; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Concerned Students of the University Community, 1988-1990; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Congressional Research Service, 1989-1991; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Consulting Initiative, Student, 1989-1990; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Constitution Series, 1988; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Creative Anachronism, Society for, 1988-1989; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Croatian and Bosnian Students, 1993; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Cultural Exchange, Princeton, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Cyprus, Students for Settlement on, 1988-1989; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - C. S. Lewis Society of Princeton University, 1985; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Daily News, 1989; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - Dialogue Magazine, 1991; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - Fashion Design, Princeton Students in, 1990; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Eretz, 1991; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - Fashion Council, Princeton, 1992; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 43)
    - Financial Forum, Princeton, 1988-1991; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 44)
    - Fisherman's Club, Princeton, 1991; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 45)
    - Flying Club, Incorporated, 1973-1988; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 46)
    - Freshman Singers, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 47)
    - George Bush Reception Committee, 1991; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 48)
    - Gay and Lesbian Union of Princeton Men's Auxiliary, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 49)
    - Gilbert & Sullivan Society, 1989-1990; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 50)
    - GO Club of Princeton, 1990; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 51)
    - Granada Sister Cities, 1989-1990; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 52)
    - Hermanas, 1989-1991; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 53)
    - Coalition Against Homophobia, 1990-1991; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 54)
    - Humanist and Liberal Caucus, 1990-1991; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 55)
    - International Music and Dance Series, 1991; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 56)
    - In the Eye, 1989-1990; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 57)
    - Iranian Students of Princeton, 1989; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 58)
    - Jewish Education, Organization for, undated; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 59)
    - Korean American Students Conference (KASCON) II, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 60)
    - Kuwait, Students for a Free, 1991; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 61)
    - Labor Solidarity Committee, 1991; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 62)
    - Lasting Peace, Students for a, 1990-1991; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 63)
    - Libertarians, Princeton, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 64)
    - Madrigal Society of Princeton, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 65)
    - M'ohr Hatorah, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 66)
    - Mathematics Club, 1990; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 67)
    - Mozart Society, 1990; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 68)
    - New Mexico, Princeton Students from, 1991; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 69)
    - Next User's Group, 1991; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 70)
    - New Jersey Governor's School Alumni Association, 1988; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 71)
    - Norman Thomas Society, 1990; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 72)
    - Objective Society, 1986-1991; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 73)
    - Operations Research Society of America - Princeton Student Chapter, undated; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 74)
    - Princeton Group for Rap Industry Protection (P-GRIP), 1991; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 75)
    - Pacific Rim Forum, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 76)
    - Palestine, Students for, 1990-1992; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 77)
    - Princeton Post, 1988; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Korean Studies, Students for, 1992; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Latino Task force, 1989-1991; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Lean on Me, 1989-1992; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Lesbian/Bisexual Women's Task Force, 1989-1990; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Los Tigres de Luevo Mexico, undated; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Orchestra, 1991-1994; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Princeton Alliance to Reverse the Arms Race (PARAR), 1989; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Princeton Scandinavian Club, 1991; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Orange Key Guide Service/McLean House, 1986; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Committee on Latin America, Princeton, 1989-1990; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Peace Curriculum, Student Committee on, undated; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Pax Christi Princeton, 1988-1991; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Poles United at Princeton, 1990; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Polish Debate, 1989; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Pretentious Art Lover, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Princeton League for Education about Anti-Semitism (PLEASE), 1990-1991; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Spray Paint, 1989-1992; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Teach for Peace, 1993-1994; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - The Princetonian Society, 1988; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Progressive Video Association, 1990; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Project Outreach, 1990; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Race Relations, Students for the Advancement of, 1991; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Reflections, 1989-1991; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Rainforest Conference, 1991; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Right to Choose, 1990-1991; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Romanian-American Society, 1990; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Rock, Rhythm, and Blues, 1993-1994; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - South-East Asian Initiative, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Special Olympics, 1989-1992; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Strokes of Genius, 1992; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Students for Asian American Studies, 1988-1991; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - The Student Coalition, 1989-1996; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Science Foundation, Princeton, 1988-1991; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Southern Club, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - Science, Technology, and Responsibility in Society (STARS), 1993; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - SPIC-MACAY, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - Students for Social Responsibility, 1989-1993; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - Student Peer Educators for Alcohol Responsibility (SPEAR), 1990-1992; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - Students on Bicker, 1987; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - Students for Multicultural Education, 1989; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - Toastmasters Club, 1992-1994; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - Tabula Rasa, 1993; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 43)
    - Theater Workshop, Students', 1989-1990; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 44)
    - Teatro '86, 1987-1991; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 45)
    - Tibetan Connection, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 46)
    - Student Volunteers Council, 1986-1992; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 47)
    - Su Magazine, 1987; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 48)
    - Switzerland, Princeton Club of, 1990; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 49)
    - Princeton Student Television, 1990-1991; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 50)
    - Telluride Association at Princeton, undated; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 51)
    - United States Troop Relief Fund, 1991; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 52)
    - Unbiased Media, Students for, 1990-1992; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 53)
    - Vietnamese Refugee Relief, 1989-1990; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 54)
    - Women Respond to the Media, 1993; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 55)
    - Urban Action, 1989; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 56)
    - The Undertaker, 1993; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 57)
    - Undergraduate Schools Committee, 1988-1989; 1 folder (Box 37, Folder 58)
  - Student Guides to Princeton, circa 1964-1994; 2 folders (Box 37, Folder 59-60)
  - Year End Report - Extracurricular Activity Lists, 1968-1969; 1 box (Box 38)
  - Reserve Officers Training Corps (R.O.T.C.), 1954-1976; 3 boxes
    - Other Institutions, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1967 September-1969 February; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1969 March-1969 August; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1969 September; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Naval Science, 1959-1971; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Air Science, 1959-1968; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Military Science, 1957-1969; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Air Force Reserve Officers Training Corps (A.F.R.O.T.C.), 1955-1968; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Naval Reserve Officers Training Corps (N.R.O.T.C.), 1956-1968; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - R.O.T.C., 1962-1968; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, 1970-1972; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Department of Defense, 1969-1971; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - R.O.T.C. Advisory Council, 1970 April 24; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - R.O.T.C. (Termination), 1964-1970; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Navy, 1969-1971; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Current II, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Spring, 1972; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - 1972-1973, 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - A.F.R.O.T.C. and N.R.O.T.C. Negotiations, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - "White Paper", 1970; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Army, 1968-1970; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Current I, 1969; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Army, 1969-1971; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - General, 1958-1969; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Air Force, 1961-1969; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Army, 1954-1970; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Navy, 1962-1971; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Association of N.R.O.T.C. Colleges, 1958-1972; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Association of N.R.O.T.C. Colleges Reports, 1965-1970; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - R.O.T.C., 1971; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - (Summary), 1970; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Air Force, 1969-1971; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - R.O.T.C., 1972-1974; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Confidential, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - R.O.T.C. Evaluation and Consolidation, 1968-1976; 1 box
      - 1976 April-May, 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Consolidation Study, 1976; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 2)